cloudwith.me 2018-02-24

# Cloudwith.me | AWS (Amazon Web Services), Azure (Microsoft Azure), Google Cloud | EC2 Cloud Hosting | WordPress

### 1 - General

It is the policy of Cloud With Me Limited (“CWM”, “we” or “us”) to comply with the Data Protection Acts, 1988 and 2003.  The purpose of this privacy statement is to outline how we deal with any personal data you provide to us while visiting CWM’s websites, apps and other applications (the “Service”).  We are committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors and / or users of the Service.  By signing up for the Service or by using the Service, you expressly consent to the collection, use, retention, processing, transfer and disclosure of your data under the terms of this privacy statement.

### 2 - Information We Collect From You

When you visit, register or use the Service you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, contact details, and credit or debit card information.We may also collect information about your usage of the Service as well as information about you from your communication with representatives of third party businesses (“Partner Business” or “Partner Businesses”) though the Service.  We may also collect specific information about your devices when using the Service, signing up for and using the Service, including, but not limited to, your device’s hardware model, operating system, web browser version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information.   When you use the Service, we may collect and store certain data, including the fact that you are accessing the Service, how that access is taking place, the dates and times of such access, where you are accessing the Service and device event information like crashes, system activity and hardware settings.

### 3 - Use of Your Personal Data

We use your data to supply you with the Service ordered by you, to bill you and to contact you about an order.  We also analyse data provided by you and others to help us administer, support and improve our business.   We may use your data to contact you to tell you about important changes or developments to the Service, or to obtain your views on the Service. Where you have agreed, we may use your data to let you know about other products and services which might be of interest to you.  If you want to stop receiving information about other products and services, you can opt out at any time by contacting us at info@cloudwith.me. At all times, access to your data by our own staff and third party intermediaries acting under our instructions or behalf, will be restricted to the bare minimum required for us to perform our business and the provision of the Service.

### 4 - International or Cross-Border Transfer of Your Personal Data and Your Express Agreement

The transfer of your data is necessary to process your registration and use of the Service, to provide updates and to respond to your inquiries.  As the internet operates in a global environment, the use of the internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international or cross-border basis.  By signing up for the Service, or by using the Services or by communicating with us, you acknowledge and expressly consent to our processing and disclosure of your personal data in this way.   By using the website, communicating with us, signing up for the Service or by using our Services, you provide your express consent to our disclosure of your personal data to our third party intermediaries for the purposes described in this privacy statement.

### 5 - Disclosure to Other People

We may pass your data to our third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage and other technology and services required to operate and maintain the Service, which may require your user’s data to be shared.  Although we own the software, codes, databases and all rights to the Service, you retain all rights to your data.   Your data may also be shared with our third party intermediaries who provide customer support.   We may disclose your data to courts and government agencies or bodies if requested to do so under a court order or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.  In addition to that, we may also share that data if we believe it is necessary to the investigation, prevention or the taking of an action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, the prevention of threats to the physical integrity of any person, violation of our terms and conditions, or as otherwise required by the law.

### 6 - Cancellations/Refunds/Disputes

Delivery Policy

Cloud With Me is a user initiated system and server installation is instant. Should your server installation fail for any reason, please contact [info@cloudwith.me](mailto:info@cloudwith.me) for assistance.

Billing and Payment

Your chosen Credit Card, Debit Card, PayPal account, CLOUD token balance, or alternative payment method will be charged immediately after your server has been installed. If you have chosen to pay for your server on a monthly subscription basis, your chosen payment method will be charged accordingly. 

Missed Payments and Server Termination

You are responsible for keeping your payment details up to date. In the event of missed scheduled payments, your server will be paused until payment has been made. Should you require any assistance in relation to missed scheduled payments, please contact [info@cloudwith.me](mailto:info@cloudwith.me). If payment is not made within 30 days of the scheduled date, your server will be terminated.

Complaints and Refund Policy

We hope that you are 100% satisfied with our service and your chosen server package. If you are dissatisfied for any reason, please contact [info@cloudwith.me](mailto:info@cloudwith.me) and we will work with you to resolve the problem. If you wish to cancel your server for a full refund, please contact us within 30 days of installation.

Termination Policy

We reserve the right to terminate a server if payment for services has not been met within 30 days of the agreed date. We reserve the right to terminate any server without warning or explanation if we have reason to believe it is being used for fraudulent purposes, unlawful activities, hate speech, general misuse, or undesirable behaviour.

### 7 - IP Addresses

An IP address is a number that is assigned to your devise automatically when you use the internet. When you visit a particular web page through the Service, our servers log your IP address. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer the Service. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

### 8 - Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information, stored in simple text files, placed on your device by a website.  Cookies can be read by the website on your subsequent visits so that you can access information faster and in a more efficient way.  The information stored in a cookie may relate to your browsing habits on the web page, or a unique identification number so that you are “remembered” on your return visit. Generally speaking, cookies do not contain personal information from which you can be identified, unless you have separately furnished such information. You can at any time set your browser to reject cookies. However if you reject our session cookies, this may affect your ability to use the Service. We use “session” cookies and “performance” cookies.“Session” cookies help users to navigate across the website’s pages. They are deleted once your leave the Service. Session cookies do not contain anything other than a session identification number which allows the webserver to “remember” where you are online. Session cookies are especially important for using the Service. Some examples of these cookies include:- identifying you as being signed in to the Service and keeping you logged in throughout your visit; \- and remembering the content of forms which you may have completed while you are on the Service.Performance cookies are used by us to provide information on the usage of the Service (details in relation to which pages users visited, how they got there, etc.). Some of these cookies are saved to your devise so that we know when you revisit the Service. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and used anonymously. We use these cookies to understand what content is popular which helps us to improve the Service. Similarly, Partner Businesses with whom you want to communicate via the Service may use cookies and other software to track information related to your communication with them.  As indicated above, it is your sole responsibility to acquaint yourself with the terms and conditions and privacy policy of that Partner Business.

### 9 - Links to third party websites

You may be made available through the Service links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by CWM.  Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites.  We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Service and to read the privacy statements of each and every third party website that collects personally identifiable information.  This privacy statement applies only to data collected by the Service.

### 10 - Security

We employ reasonable security measures to protect your data from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage.  Should a security breach occur, we will use reasonable endeavours to try to fix it.   The use of third party open sources or codes may be suggested by us to you from time to time while you visit the CWM website.   These open sources or codes are not controlled by us and your use of them is at your own risk.  CMW is not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties and we encourage you to be aware when you use these open sources or codes and to read the privacy statements of each and every of these third parties.

### 11 - Data Retention

We will retain the personal data of visitors to the Service for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.  We will retain the data of customers for as long as their account is active or as needed to the provision of the Service, but will retain and use your and your user’s data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

### 12 - Changing Your Information

You are entitled to see the information we hold about you. If you wish to see this information, please contact us at info@cloudwith.me You can also ask us to amend the information we hold about you to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date.  Please contact us at info@cloudwith.me. If you are not 100% satisfied, simply contact us within 30 days for a full refund.

### 13 - Changes To Our Privacy Statement

Our privacy statement may be modified from time to time, at CWM’s sole discretion, for any purpose deemed appropriate by us.  We will use reasonable efforts to give you prior written notice of such modifications.  In any event, any policy updates will go into effect when published.  You acknowledge and agree that it is your sole responsibility to check this page periodically to ensure that you are aware of any updates.

### 14 - Assignability

We may assign or transfer this privacy statement and your user account and related information to any person or entity that acquires or is merged with us without restriction.

### 15 - Terms and Conditions

When you sign up for the Service or use the Service, you are subject to our terms and conditions of service.  Please take time to read our terms and conditions and this privacy statement.  By proceeding further you are deemed to have read and accepted our terms and conditions and privacy statement. This privacy statement is published by Cloud With Me Limited, 39 Northumberland Rd, Ballsbridge, Dublin 4, D04 H1F3, Ireland.
